

Chawki Hadj Amor

Nationality: Tunisian Date of birth: 7 Aug 2000 Gender: Male

Phone number: (+216) 51321700

Email address: chawkiamor2555@gmail.com

in Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/chawki-hadj-amor-4a24a7210/

• Home: Boumerdes, 5110 Mahdia (Tunisia)

ABOUT ME

Self-motivated developer with 2+ years of experience in creating, maintaining, and updating solutions, I have worked with a variety of web frameworks and libraries, and I'm seeking an opportunity to expand my knowledge and shape my skills.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Information technology

Higher Institute of Technological Studies of Nabeul [15 Sep 2020 - Current]

Address: Mrezgua, 8000 Nabeul (Tunisia)

Website: https://isetn.rnu.tn/

Baccalaureate in Computer Science

High School Ibn Sina Mahdia [2015 - 2020]

SKILLS

Python

- django
- django rest framework
- beautifulSoup / selenium

JavaScript

- vue|s
- react|s
- express|s
- nodeJS

DATABASE

- sqlite
- mongoDB
- mysql
- firebase

WORK EXPERIENCE

Video surveillance technician Intern

MAXPROTECT [1 Aug 2021 – 30 Aug 2021]

City: Hammamet Country: Tunisia

Make the connectivity of surveillance cameras

Web application developer Intern

AFTERCODE [1 Feb 2022 – 28 Feb 2022]

City: Nabeul Country: Tunisia

Creation of a web application that helps students to decide on their university orientation calcule score :

calculates score

- · search by score for universities
- · contact the universities
- blog of all new about bourse ...
- search by universities (most rating universites...)

Technology used in: django

PROJECTS

Teacher management

Creation of a web application for teacher management

- add a teacher
- · assign a subject to a teacher
- · delete teacher
- · modify a teacher
- display all teachers

technology used in: springboot + angular

Laundry management

Creation of a web application for laundry:

- add client
- contact client
- notify client about his clothes status

Technology: django

web scraping

Collect data on jumia pc's and classify it by price and rating

Technology: beautifulSoup

Product management

Creation of a web application for product management

add a product

- delete product
- modify a product
- display all product

Technology: MERN

Employment

Development of a web application for the management of employment in tuinisia:

- · testing, training
- search for job
- recommendation from ai

Technology: django

Car

Development of a android application for cars management

- add car
- delete car
- update car
- display all cars
- search for car

Technology: firebase + java

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Arabic

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING B2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2

SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

French

LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1

SPOKEN INTERACTION B1

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Football

Swimming

Programming